HOWARD:
Make sure they remember, no peanuts.
(Leonard:)Howard, every Thai restaurant in town
knows you can't eat peanuts.
When they see me coming,
they go, "Ah, no-peanut boy."
- Hello, Penny, Leonard just left.
- I know, I wanna talk to you.
(Sheldon:)What would we talk about?
We have no overlapping
areas of interest I'm aware of.
- As you know, I don't care for chitchat.
- Can you just let me in?
Well, all right, but I don't see this
as a promising endeavor.
(Penny:)Okay, here's the deal.
We'll throw Leonard a kickass
surprise party for his birthday.
(Sheldon:)I hardly think so.
Leonard made it clear
he doesn't want a party.
(Howard:)Did someone say party?
(Penny:)He just doesn't know he wants one,
because he's never had one.
(Howard:)I suppose that's possible.
(Howard:)But for the record, I've never had
a threesome and yet I still know I want one.